VALENTINA FISCARELLI

UX/UI DESIGNER JUNIOR



+39 339 5801878



in valentina fiscarelli



3/08/1987



fiscarelli5@gmail.com

Born in Foggia, maker with a background in the e-commerce and online advertising (Facebook and Instagram).

After my experience in Lisbon, as a Customer Service Representative, I deepened my studies on User Experience, becoming UX/UI Design.



ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Master in UX/UI Design on Start2impact University, from 2021 until 2022;

Bachelor's degree in Letters and Philosophy, with specialising in Archaeology, at University of Foggia, 2012 - Final grade 105/110;

High School Diploma in Applied Arts at Istituto d'Arte Perugini, in Foggia 2006, final grade 90/100.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Facebook Marketing Expert in Teleperformance from 2019 to 2020 (Lisbon);

Customer Service Representative Senior in Teleperformance, from 2018 to 2019 (Lisbon);

E-commerce manager for a personal project, from 2009 to 2018 (Italy).

PROGETTI REALIZZATI COME UX/UI DESIGNER

- · Brand Identity;
- · Online medical examination booking site:
- E-commerce;
- · Online courses site;

ONLINE PORTFOLIO → fridawer.github.io/EN

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Figma/XD	
Adobe Suite	
Google Suite	
Miro	
HTML e CSS	

LANGUAGES

ITALIAN (MOTHER TONGUE)

Speaking Writing Listening

INGLESE (B2)

Speaking Writing Listening

PORTOGHESE (B1)

Speaking Writing Listening

SOFT SKILLS

· Creativity · Analytics · Empathy Precision · Problem Solving Team Work Authonomy Flessibility Calmness Leadership

Each of my work experiences has helped me develop soft skills, which I apply in my UX/UI design work.

MORE SPECIFICALLY

times of difficulty.

AS FACEBOOK MARKETING EXPERT I managed a client portfolio of small and medium-sized companies.

I talked to them to understand their needs; I studied their business in order to offer a product and advertising strategy that was advantageous as much as possible.

CONTACT WITH STAKEHOLDERS

DISCOVERY SELL

PROBLEM SOLVING

AUTHONOMY

AS CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE SENIOR I

learned to listen to the problems of customers and users, from all touch points of the purchase path (on site and off site) and at the return phase. I helped the new agents with their first tasks and in

ACTIVE AND EMPATHIC LISTENING

PROBLEM SOLVING

LEADERSHIP **TEAM WORK**

PRECISION